

# Fernando E. Jascovich

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

393, Maipú, Villa Giardino, Córdoba, 5176, Argentina

□ +54 9 3548 63 98 33 | **S** fernando.ej@gmail.com | **O** fernando-jascovich | **B** fernando-jascovich | **G** fernando-jasco

"https://www.xkcd.com/1168/"

#### **Company Recruitment Team**

June 24, 2017

GOOGLE INC. 1600 AMPHITHEATRE PARKWAY MOUNTAIN VIEW, CA 94043

#### Job Application for Software Engineer

Dear Mr./Ms./Dr. LastName,

#### About Me\_

I'm a software developer who really enjoys write scripts and see how they works. Currently I'm focused on the development of new functionalities and requirements based on the new Android APIs. I have worked with some high traffic android apps and web services. It is really exciting put the hands on different requirements based on specific targets, I had the luck of having developed native apps for startups, 1k, 18.5k and 48.5k daily active users. I do really believe that the most important thing in my career is to develop efficient algorithms based on the needs and the infrastructure of the project.

## Why Google? \_\_\_\_\_

Suspendisse commodo, massa eu congue tincidunt, elit mauris pellentesque orci, cursus tempor odio nisl euismod augue. Aliquam adipiscing nibh ut odio sodales et pulvinar tortor laoreet. Mauris a accumsan ligula. Class aptent taciti sociosqu ad litora torquent per conubia nostra, per inceptos himenaeos. Suspendisse vulputate sem vehicula ipsum varius nec tempus dui dapibus. Phasellus et est urna, ut auctor erat. Sed tincidunt odio id odio aliquam mattis. Donec sapien nulla, feugiat eget adipiscing sit amet, lacinia ut dolor. Phasellus tincidunt, leo a fringilla consectetur, felis diam aliquam urna, vitae aliquet lectus orci nec velit. Vivamus dapibus varius blandit.

#### Why Me? \_

Duis sit amet magna ante, at sodales diam. Aenean consectetur porta risus et sagittis. Ut interdum, enim varius pellentesque tincidunt, magna libero sodales tortor, ut fermentum nunc metus a ante. Vivamus odio leo, tincidunt eu luctus ut, sollicitudin sit amet metus. Nunc sed orci lectus. Ut sodales magna sed velit volutpat sit amet pulvinar diam venenatis.

Sincerely,

#### Fernando E. Jascovich

JUNE 24, 2017 FERNANDO EZEQUIEL JASCOVICH

## **Summary**

Current Full Stack Developer working freelance. 5+ years specializing in Android and 7+ years experience working with backend/infrastructure and web development. Nerd who loves emacs, Linux and enjoys to customize all of the os. Interested in solving puzzles as efficient as possible given the requirements of the project.

### Skills\_

**Programming** python, android, java, ruby, php, js, bash, elisp

**DevOps** docker, vagrant, chef

Web aws, flask, sinatra, rails, expressjs, redux, react, wordpress, html5, less, sass

Multimedia encode, stream, ffmpeg, blender, after effects, final cut, maya, 3dstudiomax, vray, mentalray, ableton, cubase, audacity

**Languages** Spanish, English

# Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

**Freelance** Remote

FULL STACK DEVELOPER Jun. 2010 - PRESENT

• Native android apps from scratch.

- Code maintaining, debugging, profiling and rework focused on performance and user experience. Integration of several third party libraries. Development of new functionalities and requirements based on the new Android APIs.
- Rewriting and code maintenance of desktop and mobile high traffic sites.
- Migration and initial setup of development environment for aws stack using docker, vagrant and chef.
- Implementation of many external providers and creation of multiple APIs for high traffic consumers using several server-side authentication and caching strategies.
- Implementation of metrics, structured-data and SEO-friendly version of sites.
- Query optimization (db, solr, elasticsearch).

**VDNMedia** Ciudad de Buenos Aires, Argentina

3D | MOTION GRAPHICS

- Modeling, texturing, lighting and 3D animation with Autodesk Maya and Blender.
- Facial and body animation with Autodesk MotionBuilder.
- 2D and 3D animation creation from integrated work on Photoshop and After Effects.
- Interactive games development on Flash (as 2.0 and as 3.0).
- 3D micro-show design for kids.
- TV shows aestethics creation.
- Video post-production.
- Audio editing.
- · Multiformat and multipurpose video editing.
- · Desktop Publishing.
- · Interactive game development for Tv shows (also including hardware and software technical support).
- Design and development of agency website.

Woler Pro&Post Ciudad de Buenos Aires, Argentina

VIDEO POST PRODUCTION / VIDEO EDITOR

Jan. 2006 - Dic. 2008

Dic. 2008 - Dic. 2010

- Lineal and non-linear video editing on multiple formats through hardware controllers and Final Cut Studio.
- 3D modeling with Autodesk Maya 2008.
- 2D and 3D animation creation from integrated work on Photoshop and After Effects.
- Aestethics and motion graphics for TV shows, internal or corporate videos on several formats.

# Education \_\_\_\_\_

Stanford University on Coursera	Remote
Graph Search, Shortest Paths, and Data Structures	Jun. 2017
<ul> <li>https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/H5JUK2A7XKHS</li> </ul>	
Stanford University on Coursera	Remote
Divide and Conquer, Sorting and Searching, and Randomized Algorithms	May. 2017
<ul> <li>https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/6JZ8J74JBV8C</li> </ul>	
Stanford University on Coursera	Remote
Cryptography I	Apr. 2017
• https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/certificate/YAGMHZ4CRB4G	
Google	Remote
DIGITAL ANALYTICS FUNDAMENTALS	Oct. 2013